

ALPER AKTAŞ FREELANCER / UNIVERSITY STUDENT

Mobile: +90 534 621 81 05 aktasalper99@gmail.com Istanbul, Turkey

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aktasalper/ https://yethranayeh.github.io/ - Portfolio

ABOUT ME

I am a 22 year old English Language and Literature student interested in software development.

I am particularly focused in Python, with intermediate knowledge of web-scraping, back-end development and database management applications.

I also have experience working on Front-end projects professionally and in my free time.

EDUCATION

Ege University
English Language and Literature | 2017 - Present

Küçükçekmece High School Foreign Language Class | 2015 - 2017

Çakmaklı Cumhuriyet High School 2013 - 2015

LANGUAGES SPOKEN

- Turkish (native)
- English

REFERENCES

Çağrı Babuçcuoğlu

Software Lead, Front-end Team Lead 1Pixel Digital Agency cagribabuccuoglu@gmail.com cagri@1pixel.im

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer Intern

1Pixel Digital Agency | Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

Freelance Video Editor

Freelancer.com | May 2020 - Aug 2021

· Creating specialized videos for people and brands

SKILLS

- Python
 - Django
 - Matplotlib
 - Selenium
 - PvQt5
 - Pandas
- Front-end Development
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - Bootstrap
 - JavaScript
 - Alpine.js
- Shopify
 - Liquid
- DBMS
 - PostgreSQL
 - SQLite
 - MongoDB

CERTIFICATES

Python (Basic Skill Assessment)

HackerRank.com | 2021 - No Expiration Date

Sıfırdan İleri Seviye Python Programlama (Python Programming: From Beginner to Advanced)

Bilgi Teknolojileri ve İletişim Kurumu | 2021 - No Expiration Date

SQL (Basic)

HackerRank.com | 2021 - No Expiration Date